(Bernadette:)Whatcha doing?
Oh!
(Howard:)Making myself a bologna sandwich
like my mom used to make me
(Howard:)after my dad left,
but before she died.
(Bernadette:)Okay, listen, I'm thinking
(Bernadette:)that maybe we can compromise
on the house.
(Howard:)I'm listening.
(Bernadette:)Let's just redo one room
and see how it goes.
(Howard:)That is reasonable.
(Howard:)But what room?
(Bernadette:)How 'bout this one?
(Howard:)No way. No, this is the room I
associate the most with my mom.
(Bernadette:)Then how 'bout the bathroom?
(Howard:)I want to change my answer.
(Bernadette:)Fine. Then the dining room.
(Howard:)I guess we didn't use it
very often.
(Howard:)Unless we had company.
(Howard:)Which didn't happen much
after my dad left and not at all
(Howard:)after my mom...
Great! I'm gonna go
pick out paint samples.
(Adam:)All right, we're just gonna
have a conversation.
(Adam:)Pretend the
camera's not here.
(Bernadette:)All right.
But this better not be
(Sheldon:)some elaborate scheme
to get me out of my shirt.